heavy.com 2015-12-31

# Privacy Policy | Heavy.com

Because your privacy is important to us, HEAVY has established procedures to protect any personal information you provide to us in accordance with the following principles:

#### A. Collecting and Sharing Personal Information:

We explicitly ask when we need information that personally identifies you (“Personal Information”). For example, HEAVY asks you for your name and e-mail address if you wish to join our mailing list, and we also may request that you provide Personal Information as part of a contest, promotion, program, or service. We may also ask for other information from time to time, such as gender and date of birth, the disclosure of which will be optional. We use your Personal Information for various purposes consistent with US law, and we may occasionally inform you of new features, services, and products. We may also collect certain non-personally identifiable information when you visit our sites, such as the type of browser you are using, the operating system you are using, and the domain name of your internet service provider. We may use this non-personally identifiable information to improve our site and to enable us to personalize your experience on HEAVY. We may also use this information in the aggregate to analyze the HEAVY site usage, as well as to offer you products, programs, or services. HEAVY does not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of thirteen (13).

#### B. “Cookies”:

We may place a text file called a “cookie” in the browser files of your computer. The cookie itself does not contain Personal Information although it will enable the HEAVY to relate your use of HEAVY to information that you have specifically and knowingly provided to HEAVY.

#### C. Disclosure of Information:

HEAVY reserves the right to release current or past member information in the event HEAVY believes that the membership is being or has been used in violation of the Terms of Service or other published guidelines or to commit unlawful acts, if the information is subpoenaed, or otherwise requested through legal process. HEAVY cooperates with law enforcement agencies in identifying those who may be using our servers or services for illegal activities. By agreeing to the conditions of this Privacy Policy and HEAVY’s Terms of Service, you hereby consent to disclosure of any record or communication to any third party when HEAVY, in its sole discretion, determines the disclosure to be appropriate. In the event your Personal Information is being sold, rented, and/or shared with any third party we will use good faith efforts to post a notice on the site clearly stating that the information is being so used and/or give you the opportunity to opt-in to authorize the use.

#### D. Consent:

By using this website and the services available to you on our site, you consent to our collection and use of your information as described above. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post the changes on this page so that you are always aware of our policies.

#### E. Links:

We may provide links to a number of other sites that we believe can offer you useful information and services. However, we are not responsible for the privacy policies of or any actions of any third parties that control the activities of such third party sites. We suggest contacting the relevant parties controlling these sites or accessing their online policies for the relevant information about their data collection.

#### F. General Information:

Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information online, that information can be collected and used by others. Therefore, when you post personal information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or from our services, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we make our best effort to ensure its security on our systems. Ultimately, you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords and for any other personal information.

If at any time you believe HEAVY has not adhered to these principles, please notify us.

#### G. 3rd Party Advertising:

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit HEAVY’s websites. The third-party advertising technology that we use on HEAVY uses information derived from your visits to HEAVY to target advertising within HEAVY. In addition, our advertisers may use other third-party advertising technology to target advertising on HEAVY’s websites or other websites. In the course of advertisements being served to you, a unique third-party cookie or cookies may be placed in your browser. In addition, HEAVY may use Web beacons, provided by third-party advertising companies, to help manage and optimize our online advertising. Web beacons enable HEAVY to recognize a browser’s cookie when a browser visits this site, and to learn which banner ads bring users to our Web site. To “opt-out,” please [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/consumer/opt_out.asp "click here").
